|<///

Krešimir Marić -Web Developer

kresimir@outlook.ie
www.kresomaric.com
+353/83/851-5011

Overview

Living in Dublin, Ireland for four years. This was an incredible experience to reach out and expand on my future. From an early age I wanted to be surrounded with technology and the word of IT but I went in other direction and finished Chef school in Croatia and worked in the industry. At the end of 2017 I started to teach myself Web Development online. After 9 months of learning and working full-time I decided to leave my job and I applied for online school OpenClassrooms. Now focusing on learning full-time and looking for opportunities to develop even more. My portfolio is based on projects from school where I was able to improve my skills.

Professional Experience

Chef de partie

Doyle Collection/The Westbury, Dublin, Ireland

- · Serving high profile customers
- · Assisting with menu development
- · Improved attention to detail

Keoghs cafe, Dublin, Ireland

Chef

Mar, 2015 – Sep, 2015

Sep, 2015 - Jul, 2018

- · Managing delivery and organising workspace
- · First job in Ireland

Chef

Apr, 2009 - Nov, 2014

Konoba Babici, Umag, Croatia

- · Gained experience working on wood based pizza oven
- · Designing the menu

Technologies

During my study with OpenClassrooms I got to work with HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Bootstrap, UML, MySqI, Git, writing technical documentations and project briefs. My main focus at the moment is to get on solid level with JavaScript and to dive into some of its frameworks. In the future I would love to learn another programming language and explore different technologies.

Education

Bachelor's-level EQF 6 "Web developer (Développeur(euse) d'application)" = "OpenClassrooms" = Dublin, Ireland = 2019

Leaving Certificate – Culinary Arts • "Antun Horvat" Trade school • Djakovo, Croatia • 2005

Certifications

Learn to code with JavaScript (OpenClassrooms) - Feb 2019

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/2516492393

Build your website with HTML5 and CSS3 (OpenClassrooms) - Nov 2018

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/5487923867

Build quick and beautiful WordPress sites (OpenClassrooms) - Oct 2018

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/9590507750

Understanding the Web (OpenClassrooms) - Oct 2018

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/2947433099

Think like a computer: Understanding the logic of programming (OpenClassrooms) - May 2019

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/3877891772